(THIS SERIES IS AN ADULT ANIMATION INTENDED FOR
VIEWERS WHO ARE OF LEGAL AGE
ACCORDING TO LOCAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS.)
(THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL AND BEARS
NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR EVENTS.)
(ALL CHARACTERS ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF CONSENT.)
(THE TITLE MAY CONTAIN SENSITIVE CONTENT
SUCH AS SEXUAL OR VIOLENT SCENES. DO NOT IMITATE.)
So the preparations...
are complete, right?
Yes sir.
All related departments have been notified,
and the news will be out tomorrow.
required a considerable amount of money.
I'm afraid FS ended up
getting the short end of the stick.
It's necessary
for the sake of our long-held ambition.
Please excuse me.
Long-held ambition, huh?
Finally...
the time has come.
NUKITASHI THE ANIMATION
Just the failed creations
of the ones before
Some rebel elements,
rotten to the core
Beyond the wire fence,
a world of sleek design
I stared it down,
a secret that was only mine
Inside the perfect world
that someone else designed
If we were different,
we were always left behind
In a gentle world for everyone to behold
Someone untold cried in agony
Just a laughing mob,
a mindless flock of crows,
Always saying "NO"
to things that nobody knows
With values and with normalcy they pose
Armed with all their theories, I suppose
And then they call us useless pros
Even if you know
that you are in the wrong
Remember what it means
to live your life and to be strong
If you truly wish
you could change today right now
With that very heart,
go on and show them
Don't you hesitate,
don't ever stop
Destroy it,
make the whole world drop
With all that passion,
pierce right through it all
Go anywhere you want
Can't even love yourself?
Of the impatience or the mess you've made
Because right here and now,
we're standing tall
We are alive and breathing after all
RESIGNATION LETTER
Why?
Give me an explanation I can accept.
It's about the Coming-of-Sex day.
Even though it was a...
once-in-a-lifetime chance
to crush the enemy,
Desertion in the face of the enemy is...
execution by firing squad.
We are not an army.
Even if it's true
that you left your post...
I'm just a spineless coward.
It'd be better if
FS doesn't have someone like me.
Don't be ridiculous!
Do you have any idea how much money...
and effort it took to make you competent?
You're overthinking it.
Touka-chan is always restless
and wandering off somewhere.
That's right,
I tend to wander off.
My sister's condition is getting worse.
I want to be by her side
as much as possible.
For training me in such a short time,
I am truly grateful.
Take that with you.
It's a proof of your time in FS.
I'll hold on to the bullets.
Come back when your sister gets better.
Whenever you are ready.
Excuse me.
So he's left.
What do we do with this resignation letter?
We have to respect his decision, don't we?
So please come back
of your own free will.
Senpai.
Everyone, I'm truly sorry.
I couldn't stick to my beliefs.
I couldn't cast aside my feelings.
I couldn't send Fumino off.
Tachibana-san.
It's all my fault.
Therefore, I will take responsibility.
You can't do that!
Stop, stop, stop.
Calm down, Tachibana-san.
Let go of me!
If I don't do this,
I can't face you all!
No good, the weight difference
is too great.
Master!
Leave it to me!
Here I come!
Jun, stop this foolishness.
It's true that this time,
it's your fault.
But I also share the same responsibility.
So, I'll face the consequences with you!
Wait, wait, stop this foolishness.
He has regained his senses.
So she used poison to fight poison.
Don't stop me.
If this is the only way to save you...
then I have no choice
but to share the pain.
Your love is too intense, Nanase-san.
More importantly,
the usual stuff has arrived.
I am disappointed in you warriors.
Regarding the handover of Fumino,
it will take a few days to prepare again.
If you fail next time,
all aid will be cut off.
"Cut off aid" means...
A vasectomy?
It's cost-cutting.
Does that mean
we can't gather here anymore?
If we lose our weapons and base,
fighting back won't even be an option.
Please sign!
Everyone, please sign the petition.
Let's bring the precious culture
of Seiran Island to all of Japan.
- Please sign!
- Thank you very much!
On top of spreading your legs,
you want to spread your culture too?
Then I'll spread your XXX too.
My XXX will be spread all over the country.
The wave of lewd sex is far from stopping,
but it's continuing to spread.
Aah... Bee... Cum!
Are you practicing your ABCs now?
Get pregnant D-E-F-G!
If this continues,
we'll be swallowed by the wave of lewd sex.
Too rough!
Too rough, your hair is falling!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
The hair is cumming back!
We have no choice but to hand over Fumino.
But if we do that, FS will...
Ah, Banapaisen.
If it isn't Nekobana-kun.
I'm just Tachibana.
I'm no longer in FS.
I've heard about it.
But you are always Nekobana-kun.
Are you on duty?
We're putting up wanted posters.
HEY YOU DICKS!
Is this...
SEEKING INFO OF A DICK WITH SIMILAR SHAPE!
my dick?
Incredible!
Magical dick?
The shape is insane!
This is crazy!
The person who finds this dick will...
get a cash prize
and our prized family jewels.
This is what you call a "head" hunter!
Su su su.
This is a secret from SHO,
but we're in the middle
of "Magical Dick Capture Operation."
If it can drive all women crazy,
it's as good as
controlling half of humanity.
Such a dangerous dick.
Just a mere prick...
There's no way it has that kind of power...
No, it's true that...
my life has been ruined by this dick.
Keep cumming! Keep cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I wonder if Tachibana-san is okay.
Jun may seem like that,
but he has a pretty introspective side.
In times like these,
he needs someone to kick him into shape.
You know him well, Katagiri-san.
What to do?
There must be a way.
There must be something.
Excuse me, can we talk about dicks?
That wanted poster,
it's your dick, isn't it?
It's the one
rumored to be the magical dick.
That's...
Actually, we've been tearing them down
as much as we can.
So you can rest easy.
Aren't I a good senpai?
Tearing down official SHO posters
without permission is...
a violation of
the Reproductive Occupation Act.
I've become a bad senpai.
You've got some good friends,
don't you, Jun?
Yeah.
I'll handle the rest.
I'll manage it somehow.
Is that the final decision?
Yes, we just received
a notification from SHO.
Apparently, they've invested
a huge amount into that plan from SHO...
so the FS downsizing is really happening.
Is there no way to stop it?
If we had something to give us
an advantage over SHO, then perhaps.
Don't you have a way
to find the magical dick?
I already have it.
What shall we do, Touka-sama?
We'll have to use
a slightly forceful method,
but it can't be helped.
SEEKING INFO OF A DICK WITH SIMILAR SHAPE!
- Ikuko.
- Huh?
Get squad 1 ready to deploy!
Okay.
Well then.
Magical dick.
Hey, there's a place I want to go.
Huh?
Going though here
is the only shortcut, but...
it's too dangerous at this time.
Let's strip.
Eh? Wait...
Nanase?
How did it come to this?
It can't be helped.
I have to do this to hide your dick!
- Hey, is that...
- What?
The sea of people is parting
before her XXX aura.
The aura of XXX XXX.
Even my XXX is going to split.
Why didn't we take the long way?
That's because...
you kept making that face.
Eh?
Enough, let's just go.
This place is...
You remember it, right?
The place where you first told me
about your past.
You're thinking so much
your head's about to explode.
Nanase.
It's okay to backtrack a little.
Why don't you try letting it all out?
Before... I told you here, didn't I?
That I was being bullied.
Yes, you did.
Oh.
The reason I became XXX...
wasn't just because of the bullying.
Look, such a disgusting dick.
It's so huge,
they should be taxing that thing!
If you put that thing inside,
the grossness will rub off!
Is that the moan button?
You're Tachibana-kun, right?
Nukitashi.
You shouldn't worry about things like that.
But everyone said so.
My mom said that being tall
or having a pretty face...
is a part of your individuality.
But no one said that
having a big dick is an individuality.
Then I'll say it for you.
That is your individuality, Tachibana-kun.
Hah?
Hey, why don't we become comrades?
Comrades?
Yeah, comrades.
That means friends.
Let's be friends.
Yeah.
We played together a lot.
My mother was always busy
taking care of the sickly Asane.
So she was my only friend.
But she was bullied too.
Because she questioned
the lewd sex of Seiran Island.
Sex should be
with someone you truly love.
That's what I think.
I don't care what anyone else says.
But if the bullying continues...
It's okay.
I'm good at sports.
Next time, I'll beat them up.
If she accept lewd sex,
she wouldn't have to suffer like this.
Rather than seeing her being forced to
have sex by someone on the island,
I have to be the one to save her.
Ah, what?
Tachibana-kun?
I...
- have to save her.
- Wait.
It hurts, stop it.
Let me go.
Wait...
Tachibana-kun.
I have to save...
Noooo!
S-Sorry.
Wait, Tachibana-kun.
Later I heard from rumors that
she had transferred schools.
I had to save that girl.
That's what I thought.
But I must have been strongly interested
in lewd sex subconsciously.
At that time, I was already trapped
in the cage of peer pressure.
Sex should only be with
someone you truly love.
With a mindset like that,
she must have thought
the me from that day was disgusting.
I couldn't forgive myself.
I hated myself from the bottom of my heart
for getting an erection.
That's why...
this time, I must continue to resist
lewd sex and peer pressure.
That's what I swore to myself, but...
Seems like that girl
has returned to this island.
Hah?
About two years ago, I think.
She decided to enroll in Minotsuki Academy.
Because she went to a real girls' school,
so she started dressing in a bitchy style.
Her old classmates
didn't seem to recognize her.
That girl...
She always regretted
rejecting you out of fear that day.
No matter how low the chances,
she kept waiting.
For the day she could meet
her first love again.
She had changed so much
that he didn't recognize her either.
But she could feel his regret painfully.
Trapped in his hatred of lewd sex,
he had become a twisted virgin.
She knew he was suffering.
This time for sure...
I would be the one to support you.
Nanase.
Jun, that is why...
You're...
Rather, Tachibana-kun.
No matter what happens,
I'll be your ally.
Even if the whole world comes to hate you,
I'll die for you.
This time, for sure.
Nanase...
These glasses are really convenient.
Erection status checked.
Magical dick compatibility rate: 1919%.
FS Squad 1.
What? Is that Nanase Katagiri-dono?
The Legendary XXX?
That's impossible.
Why is that?
There's a saying.
On Seiran Island,
impossible things happen quite often.
In other words,
she really is Katagiri-dono.
What are they saying?
Jun, we're running for it.
Wow, are those fireworks?
They could also be steam.
NULL Base, this is Atom 1.
We've made unexpected
contact with enemy's cunts.
Currently in retreat, but at this rate...
I won't let you escape!
Jun.
Nanase.
Looks like the party's over.
You mean "the real party's just
getting started", right?
My indecisiveness has put Nanase
through this again.
It's okay, Jun.
You're not wrong.
Hah?
Now, there are many comrades...
many friends to help you out, right?
- Nanase.
- That's why.
Whatever you desire, what you believe in...
just do it!
Nanase!
Big brother!
I was...
You were washed all the way to the harbor.
I had to give you a ride back
on my anal-bike.
Luckily, I had a good grasp
of the ocean currents.
Nanase.
Where's Nanase?
Tachibana-san, what are you going to do?
I'm going to get Nanase back.
And then we're leaving the island.
- With Fumino, we still have a chance...
- Wait.
Something insane is happening.
Breaking news.
The New Lewd Law, which will make...
lewd sex possible nationwide,
has been approved.
With the catchphrase "Let's have sex
all over Japan this summer,"
lewd sex will be promoted nationwide.
What does that mean?
As a model case for the new law,
it is being considered to rename
Yokohama City to YokoXXX City,
Ibaraki Prefecture to IXXX Prefecture.
What does that mean?
And now for the next news.
The Anti-Copulation Force that has been
causing trouble in Seiran Island...
has been taken into custody.
The ringleader is known as
the Legendary XXX, Nanase Katagiri.
She is currently being
interrogated by SHO authorities.
N-Nanase-san.
I repeat.
The ringleader of the Anti-Copulation Force
who was taken into custody...
is believed to be Nanase Katagiri.
This erorist,
terrorist against eroticism...
is scheduled to be executed
by guillotine in the coming days.
Hey, it has been a while
We finally met again
I wonder,
have you been doing okay
Just kidding! So happy,
but I'm also blushing
Hey, maybe not this one
maybe not that one too
I fret about the little things I've done
Will you even notice
I tried my very best
to dress up nicely for everyone
Should I be bold and make a move
No guarantee that you will approve
It's all or nothing? I can't do that
Ahhh, I think I have fallen flat
This story that I share with you
Has way too many options
Got to make my mind up and be brave
So the role of heroine is mine to be
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Cause even I am so in love with you
A cliché story's not the thing for me
And laying plot points, how can that be
Worry, worry, worry, and then fall
Keep worrying and falling
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Don't forget the promise that we made
I'm just kidding, a sweet lie is okay
Actually, what I want is the real thing
Ahhh... I'm begging, please love me